( Watch on www.kissasia.biz or asiankh.org )
♪Hey, you, you, you, why is it you again?♪
♪Always stumbling upon my little secrets♪
♪Falling on my brows, my lashes, even the strands by my mouth♪
♪Like my favorite kitten on a rainy spring afternoon♪
♪Hey, you, you, you, why is it you again?♪
♪You effortlessly awaken my protective instincts♪
♪Hitting all my little thoughts, my doubts, and my temper♪
♪Like my favorite beer and fried chicken in autumn, or spicy boiled fish in winter♪
♪Why is it you again? That sweet way you speak♪
♪As if the whole world knows my mind is full of you♪
♪Why is it still you? That secret smile behind your cool facade♪
♪I might as well play along. Let me protect you♪
♪Why is it always you? The smile at the corner of your lips♪
♪Before I knew it, the words blurted out, "I like you. I only like you."♪
=Love Has Fireworks=
(Based on "Investment Men and Women" by Hong Er on Jinjiang Literature City)
=Episode 1=
I don't care where we meet.
I have to see him today.
I'll wait for your update.
(But before the turning point arrives, the market is still under big pressure.)
(The packed morning rush hour)
(is Shanghai's embrace)
(for every office worker.)
(Then, it carries you to where you need to go.)
(This is Lujiazui.)
(World Financial Center) (China's financial hub.)
(A global financial powerhouse.)
(The people who work here all carry themselves with confidence and drive.)
Hello?
Yes. Okay. Thank you.
I'll be right there.
Sorry. Sorry.
Welcome.
Hello, sir.
How may I help you?
I'd like to buy a purse. For a woman.
Certainly. This way, please.
Right over here.
You can take a look at these.
Look at the stitching. Feel the fabric. It's marvelous.
Only a suit like this is worthy of him.
Your boyfriend is a lucky man.
He won't be my boyfriend for much longer.
Congratulations in advance.
Thank you.
Alright. I'll take it.
Please wrap it up. It's a gift.
Alright, sir. This way, please.
Excuse me.
May I sit here?
Thank you.
Excuse me. I'd like the same noodle dish as this gentleman.
Mr. Ma, hello.
Hello.
I'm from Zhizhong Construction Investment. My name is Li Yifei.
Here's my business card.
You know me?
Actually, I've wanted to meet with you for a long time.
But I heard your schedule in Shanghai has been packed,
So I could only catch you during lunch.
You want to invest in me?
What was your firm again?
Zhizhong Construction Investment.
But the one interested in your company is me personally.
I'd like to ask, how much are you planning to raise this round?
Twenty million.
Twenty million?
Sounds good. Tell me about your plan first.
Let's talk about your budget.
Over here.
Excuse me,
Another bowl of tomato pork-bone noodles.
Thank you.
Didn't you ask me to pack it for you?
Why are you eating it yourself?
If I'd waited for you,
I would've starved to death.
Weren't you just dropping off some documents?
Why did you go shopping?
I didn't want to take any chances.
It's a limited edition. Too bad if someone bought it before I did.
Tomorrow is his birthday.
I'm giving this to him.
Right on time.
Limited edition, my foot.
It's scarcity marketing.
Look at you.
You won't even order takeout
To save on the delivery fee.
What has Wang Ruohai ever done to deserve you spending this much on him?
He works at a bank.
He needs a few nice outfits.
It's investing in his image.
He works at a bank, but you work in investment banking.
Why does he get the limited-edition stuff
While you're pinching pennies every day?
I...
I just work at the back office crunching data.
I'm perfectly fine dressing like this.
Also,
There might be another surprise coming.
Surprise?
What surprise?
Uh...
Sorry, sir.
So sorry.
A second ago, they were talking about a twenty-million investment,
And now he's apologizing.
Sorry.
It's okay. It's a knockoff. It wasn't expensive.
I can pay for it.
No, no need.
Hello?
Ms. Fang?
Alright.
I've got to go.
- You haven't finished your lunch yet. - No time.
Sorry.
Boss, I knew you'd be here. Why aren't you answering your phone?
- What's wrong? - Something big happened.
What happened?
(Zhizhong Construction Investment Securities Co., Ltd)
Is everything ready?
Yes.
Ms. Fang, Huang Shusong has been taken away by the police.
He's not the only one at Zhizhong.
Get ready.
Yes.
- Where's Qian Fei from the back office? - I've notified her.
She should be here any minute.
Keep calling her.
Yes.
You wanted to see me, Ms. Fang?
Let's go.
Go where?
Enough questions. Just come with her.
Let's go.
Ms. Fang.
I didn't know Huang was involved in so many shady dealings.
You never worked with him,
So you probably don't know.
He was in charge of the IPO bid for Shanlifang Hotel Group.
The deadline is 2 PM today.
These are the materials on Shanlifang Hotel Group.
Take a quick look at it.
What do you mean? Handing the project to me?
Aren't there other teams?
The chairman of Shanlifang specifically asked for you.
What?
Mr. Liao specifically asked for me?
That's right. Liao Jinshan.
You know him?
Who doesn't know him?
Who are we up against?
Hejing Securities.
Jumbo from the back office who exposed Huang Shusong
Was you, right?
I didn't expose him.
I analyzed some public data
And pointed out a few obvious issues.
No need to be modest.
That devious fox
Is extremely cautious.
The fact that you managed to find clues at all is impressive.
You deserve a lot of credit for his arrest.
- How much longer, Boss? - Almost done.
You're revising the proposal at the last minute.
That's a huge gamble.
Mr. Liao specifically asked for me.
Of course, I need to show my value.
Okay.
Those from Zhizhong aren't here yet.
The bidding ends at 2 PM.
Guard all the entrances and exits. Stop them.
If they miss the bidding, they'll be disqualified.
I'll send you the plate numbers of the cars they usually use.
Keep your eyes open.
There are so many people here.
If I were them, I definitely wouldn't come through the front entrance.
You're not them.
How would you know?
Enough chatter. Better safe than sorry.
Let's go.
(Exit)
They're here.
Perfect timing. Get out.
They asked me to keep an eye on those from Zhizhong.
How could I cover so many entrances by myself?
Sorry.
Are you okay?
You?
You!
- You... - You...
You...
Aren't you...
Twenty million!
What twenty million?
I get it now.
You've been following me since this morning.
Not bad.
Your firm has really gone all out.
What?
You cast a whole net just to catch me?
You know what? There's no guarding against me.
Is this guy a joke or what?
What's his problem?
(Naranmad Bank)
For a loan of only ten million.
The chairman's daughter doesn't need to show up in person every time.
Maybe Mr. Wang
Is more attractive than the loan itself.
This way, please, Ms. Liao.
Am I early?
No.
The contract is ready. Let's sit down and talk.
(Bid Documents)
Everyone, relax. There's still one minute left.
Sorry. I hope I'm not late.
Please have a seat.
Sit.
I'm Li Yifei from Zhizhong.
This is our proposal.
(Bid Documents)
I'll have Legal review it one more time.
You'll have our answer within three days.
Personally, I don't see any issues.
I trust you with it.
Thank you for your trust, Ms. Liao.
Ms. Fang,
May I know
Why you brought me to the bidding today?
Answer my question first.
You graduated top of your class from
University of Finance & Economics, right?
You've done well at Hejing.
In the past three years, none of the projects you've worked on
Has needed rework.
Yet, you've been content to stay in the back office.
Not long ago, you even turned down HR's offer
To transfer to my project team.
Why?
Because
I'm getting married.
Thanks for helping with the loan.
To celebrate our successful partnership, how about dinner tonight?
Tonight, I...
It's settled then.
Okay.
Love doesn't last forever.
It doesn't stay the same.
Marriage isn't insurance for love.
A wife's place
Isn't irreplaceable either.
That's just your opinion.
Having a happy family
Is my goal.
It's his goal, too.
I believe that we're irreplaceable
In each other's hearts.
I'm certain of that.
To each their own. I'm not trying to force you.
I'm just reminding you not to waste your talent.
I thought you had more room to grow.
Ms. Fang,
I really appreciate what you told me today.
It's just that
Everyone has their own priorities.
Right, here's your membership card.
Just leave it there.
Do you know how much time you've spent on all this?
What a waste of time. What a waste of your life.
You know what?
You're the third person today to tell me I'm wasting my time.
So, in your eyes,
Am I really that hopeless?
Of course.
People aren't blind.
You're putting your energy into some guy,and you've made no progress at all.
You'll regret it sooner or later.
Actually, I was recognized.
You know?
Ms. Fang invited me to join her project team.
Really? That's great.
Don't tell me you turned it down again.
Of course I did.
Those project teams
Work people to death.
They have no life
Outside of work.
Why would I join them?
You know what?
People like us with a regular nine-to-six, five-day workweek
Are rare.
Honestly,
I don't even know what to say to you anymore.
You're out of your mind.
(Homeowner Signature: Qian Fei)
Thank you.
I'm really satisfied.
Thank you for your support.
If you have any issues, feel free to contact the after-sales team.
- Alright. Thanks. I'll walk you out. - I won't trouble you.
Thank you.
Alright. Goodbye.
Bye.
This is wonderful!
I finally have a place of my own.
How long do you think it'll take
To sell my apartment?
Your asking price
Is a little high,
But compared to the market price,
It's quite a bargain.
It should sell quickly.
I only have one requirement.
Full payment.
Right. Keep an eye out
For a rental apartment for me.
No problem.
As for the requirements, they're the same ones I just mentioned.
Got it. Don't worry.
We've got plenty of listings.
- You again? - You again?
Well, well. You even followed me here.
Are you going to stop?
Followed you?
I was just passing by.
Finally caught you.
What do you want?
You broke my phone.
Pay up.
It looks perfectly fine.
I just got it repaired today...
Come up with a better excuse next time.
You!
How about we grab dinner tonight?
Let's go.
No thanks. Well...
I have plans later.
Alright then.
I really enjoyed talking with you today.
You sure you don't need a ride?
No, really. Thank you.
Okay. I'll get going.
Drive safe.
Have fun.
Will do.
Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow night.
What took you so long?
I'm starving.
Fei!
What's wrong?
I love you so much!
How did you know I don't have a new purse
For next week's event?
This isn't for you.
Jun's parents are celebrating their 30th wedding anniversary.
I picked it out for his dad.
You never go shopping with me, but you'll shop for someone else's gift.
Next time, okay?
Didn't I come have dinner with you?
Jeez!
(Art Center)
Ruohai.
Do you remember
That you once saved a girl?
It was you?
I never expected
That after all these years,
You'd still be so beautiful.
Those years during my teens
Were the darkest time of my life.
Your bright and cheerful spirit gave me so much support.
After all these years,
You're still just as cheerful.
You've got so much fight in you.
Hello, Hai?
Guess where I am right now.
I'm at our new house.
I'm really happy with the renovation. The colors are lovely.
You're almost here, right?
Alright. I'll let you get on.
Your client comes first.
I'll wait for you at home.
I have a surprise for you.
Okay.
I'll wait up for you.
Here.
Open this champagne.
Your benefits for the second half of the year
Are probably going to be pretty limited.
Do you really think you're some rich kid?
You'd better off focusing on how to splurge.
Even my dad
Doesn't trust me that much.
You have your own struggles, too.
That's why I need someone I can trust
To stay by my side
And help me wholeheartedly.
And that person is you.
I... How do you want me to help?
I'd like to invite you to join Shanlifang
As the Finance Director.
Would you give me that honor?
I can't do that.
A Finance Director is completely different
From what I'm doing now.
I'm afraid I won't be up to it.
This loan project has proven your abilities.
Not just me, my dad thinks highly of you, too.
He's acting cautiously.
He's almost won her over.
What are you on about?
I mean that guy.
Look at his face. He looks so guilty.
He's probably sneaking out on a date.
I hate sneaky people.
You really have too much free time.
So green.
A greenland. Healthy greens.
Detoxifying and good for the skin.
Here.
After dinner,
Go home and pack our things.
I'm moving.
Getting a new place?
Not a new place. I'm short on money,
So I sold the apartment.
With your current income, you can't possibly...
Are you worried
That once I don't own a place,
I'll be even less worthy of you?
Why would I be worried?
We can just break up.
I'm really touched
By your gaslighting.
Where are you going to live after this?
I'm renting a place.
Renting?
Li Yifei, have you never thought about
Marrying me?
You were the one who said
You wanted to stay a girl forever.
You wouldn't think about marriage before turning forty.
You told me not to overthink it. Wasn't that what you said?
I can think that way,
But you can't have no plans at all.
You've never planned on giving me a home.
You don't plan on getting married,
But I have to stay ready to marry you anytime
And prepare a big house for you.
How is that fair?
I just want you to love me
A little more than I love you.
Is that so wrong?
We're preparing for an IPO right now.
At Shanlifang,
In less than three years,
You can achieve what would take
Ten or even twenty years at a bank.
I know this is a major decision.
You shouldn't rush it.
Give yourself some time.
The world is big.
But if you trap yourself,
Your world becomes very small.
Shanlifang is the perfect stage for you to show what you're capable of.
Let's work side by side
And build a different future for it.
Alright?
(Happy Birthday, Hai. We'll be together forever!)
Ruohai,
I saw a watch today.
Try it on for me.
Who are you buying it for?
This watch is a gesture of goodwill. I'd like to invite you to join us.
Wear it when you're hesitating.
I hope it'll help you make your decision.
You're awake.
You're back.
Finally. You must be tired.
I was with a client.
It's past midnight.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Look. I wrote you a card.
I read it.
Open the gift. You're definitely going to love it.
Come on. Open it.
I'll look at it later.
Alright.
Come here.
We finally have a place of our own.
What do you think? Isn't the color scheme lovely?
We finally have somewhere to call home.
No more drifting around without a place to belong.
I have something important to tell you.
What is it?
Here I go.
I switched jobs.
I joined a new company as the Finance Director.
Finance Director?
Is it a solid company?
Yeah. It's big.
That's great news.
Why are there
So many good things happening today?
It's your birthday,
We got our new home,
And now you've got a new job.
Is there another piece of good news?
Nope.
That's all?
What's it about?
Are you upset?
- No. - It's fine, Qian Fei.
If you want to say something, just say it.
Well...
I thought you were going to propose today.
Why... Why would you think that?
It's because
Your mom called me the other day.
She said you were planning to propose
And told me to book the wedding venue.
So I paid the deposit.
Nobody told me anything about this.
My mom was trying
To force us to get married?
No.
Qian Fei, why didn't you tell me?
Because I thought you were planning to surprise me,
So I pretended I didn't know.
But look,
The wedding venue is already booked,
And we took wedding photos last time...
Fei, don't you remember?
We were supposed to take a couple's photoshoot.
You said the wedding outfits looked nice and wanted to try them on.
So we casually took a few pictures.
That doesn't count.
If that doesn't count,
Surely this apartment does?
Your dad bought this apartment.
I'm a man.
How can I marry you
While living in a place your dad bought?
Your dad paid for it.
What era are we living in?
Don't overthink it, okay?
My family paid the down payment,
But you've been making the mortgage payments every month, too.
Speaking of that mortgage,
Do you know how much pressure I'm under every day?
Fei.
Come here. Sit.
There's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
Go ahead.
We bought this apartment
At a really good price.
I checked recently.
It's probably gone up by at least 500,000.
If...
I'm just saying if.
If we sold it
And invested the money,
Wouldn't that make more sense
For our situation right now?
We're struggling way too much now.
Wait. Are you saying you want to sell this apartment?
Weren't we struggling when we got kicked out
In the middle of the night back then?
That was when I made up my mind
That I had to have a place of my own
Where nobody could ever throw me out.
Fei, things are different now.
I'm a Finance Director now.
Trust me.
I'll be doing really well within three years.
I'll buy a bigger, better home
For you.
We'll take the best wedding photos
And have the most beautiful wedding, okay?
No, that's not what I mean.
What I'm saying is
That we worked hard for years
To finally have this apartment.
We both treasure it.
Why would we just sell it like that?
How can you be so sure
You'll be able to buy a better place later?
You're right.
I can't.
At the end of the day,
You just don't believe me.
No. That's not what I mean.
♪Whenever I look up♪
♪I meet your gaze, those eyes♪
♪I wish to hold on to that light of joy♪
♪And embrace that fleeting happiness♪
♪Sometimes we cry, sometimes we laugh♪
♪Sometimes we're swept away by sweetness♪
♪Sometimes we run♪
(Qian Fei: I'm home. Where are you?)
Why did I argue with him?
(Qian Fei: Hai, it's your birthday today.)
(I don't want to talk about anything else.)
(I just want to wish you a happy birthday and happiness always.)
♪I've never known a love as warm as yours♪
♪Nothing more needs to be said, I won't let go of you♪
(Alarm)
(I'm home. Where are you?)
Why are you here?
Is this about our work next month?
I'm not here to talk about work.
I'm here to talk about last night.
What about last night?
Run in place. Come on.
Is that Wang Ruohai?
Who's that woman?
They already left.
I'm telling you, if Lu Ze hadn't stopped me,
I would've gone over there and slapped you.
Maybe you should find out what actually happened first.
She's my client.
Just a client.
Yes, just a client.
Do you have to hug and cuddle a client after dinner?
If that's all you came here
To talk about,
Please leave.
You've got some nerve, Wang Ruohai.
Tonight,
You'd better explain everything to Fei.
Otherwise, you'll regret it.
Don't worry.
I'll clear things up with her tonight.
Good. Don't drag it out.
Yeah.
I've been apartment hunting lately.
I have no idea what was going through his head.
He poured all his money into it.
Now he's got nothing left in savings.
He's basically living paycheck to paycheck.
Hang on.
(Protect Hard-Earned Money)
In the north, there are the Chaoyang Aunties.
In the south, there are the Jiangpu Uncles.
We'll protect people's hard-earned money
And never give scammers a chance.
- Bravo! - Bravo!
Let me introduce someone.
This is my childhood friend, Li Yifei.
A real financial expert from Lujiazui.
If you have any questions,
Feel free to consult him.
For more anti-fraud information, please follow our official account
Or scan the QR code in our handbook.
Thank you, everyone.
Good!
Ms. Liao.
I guess you've bought the answer I want.
I told you. It's a good gesture.
Seeing you wear it puts my mind at ease.
I've thought it over carefully. I've decided to join Shanlifang.
Thank you for giving me this opportunity, Ms. Liao.
Congratulations. You made the right decision.
Thank you for inviting me.
I'll be counting on your support from now on.
We should be celebrating today,
But I have a banquet I must attend.
Why don't you come with me?
Sure.
There probably isn't enough time to go home and change.
We should just buy something.
The company can cover it.
I'll be your fashion assistant.
I'll leave everything to you, Ms. Liao.
Is this your girlfriend?
Yes.
She's cute.
You should get a new wallet, too.
As you wish.
How about this one?
Looks nice.
I'll pack your wallet
Together with your clothes.
Is that okay?
Sure.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you for sending me home, Ms. Liao.
It's nothing.
I was feeling a little stuffy
And needed some fresh air.
I'll take a walk with you.
Sounds good.
Hello, Jingjing?
You finally picked up.
I was baking this afternoon.
I didn't hear my phone.
I've been busy all the way until tonight.
Okay. Did Wang Ruohai talk to you?
About what?
He hasn't contacted me.
Didn't even call you?
No.
We had a fight last night.
Happy birthday, Ruohai.
Thank you.
As your client,
I can't be too affectionate.
But on your next birthday,
And the birthday after that,
And every birthday after that,
I hope I can celebrate with you,
Finance Director.
Thank you, Ms. Liao.
You see,
He even called off the wedding banquet.
I'm telling you, he's seeing someone else.
Don't say that.
I'm serious. I saw him last night.
He was acting very intimately with a woman.
No way.
Anyone could cheat, but not my Hai.
I'll get going.
How long have you been here?
Not long.
Um,
I made this cake for you.
Ask your question.
This watch...
Did she give it to you for your birthday?
It's from her,
But it's not a birthday gift.
What is it then?
I can't really explain it.
Do we not trust each other now?
I do trust you.
Of course, I trust you.
If you say right now that you'll always stay with me,
That you'll marry me, I'll believe you.
So the only way for me to prove I'm innocent
Is to propose to you here and now?
I'm not forcing you.
You're not?
The wedding venue was booked.
Was that my mom's idea, or yours?
If you're going to keep pushing me like this,
Maybe we should just break up.
What did you say?
Break up?
Let's break up.
We don't have a common goal.
We can't understand each other.
We don't even have basic trust anymore.
What's the point of being together?
=Love Has Fireworks= (Next Episode Preview)
Who are you?
Let's go.
Come on.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Fine.
I'm done arguing with you.
Ever since I met you, I've had the worst luck.
Let's go, Gui Lili.
Even if she gives us our rent back,
We probably won't find a better place.
What are you doing?
Stop already!
♪There's no need to know the ending from the start♪
♪Let the melody play through the chords with the wind♪
♪There's no need to keep every promise from the past♪
♪Leave some surprises for the unknown in life♪
♪There's no need to force things between two people♪
♪Perhaps I'll feel alone, yet still find you there for me♪
♪There's no need to dwell on right or wrong, nor fear♪
♪A hug means more than countless apologies♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly like the stars and the moon on high♪
♪I'll send you into the wide world♪
♪To live with passion and become who you truly are♪
♪A quiet shoulder♪
♪Like a harbor waiting for your wandering soul♪
♪I'll wait for the day you return to a simpler life♪
♪The lights of home warm the night♪
♪A companionship that lasts forever♪
♪Shining brightly like the stars and the moon on high♪